- name: "Prima"
  key: 1
  search-options:
    size: 3
  settings:
    highlight: matches
#    randomize-exercise-order: no
  grammar: "NovoModoPrima"
  languages:
    solution: "PrimaLat"
    problem: "PrimaEng"
  exercises:
    - solution: "vinum sapiens est"
      problem: "he is wise"
    - solution: "Augustus imperium tenet"
      problem: "the emperor holds the empire"
    - solution: "Augustus felix est"
      problem: "the friend is lucky"
    - solution: "Augustus felix est"
      problem: "the father is lucky"
#    - solution: "Augustus imperator est"
#      problem: "Augustus is a friend"
#    - solution: "Augustus amicus est"
#      problem: "Augustus is the emperor"
#    - solution: "Augustus imperator est"
#      problem: "Augustus is the father"
#    - solution: "Augustus pater est"
#      problem: "Augustus is the emperor"
#    - solution: "Caesar Augustus Galliam vincit"
#      problem: "the emperor Augustus conquers Africa"
#    - solution: "Caesar Augustus Africam vincit"
#      problem: "the emperor Augustus conquers Gaul"

- name: "Prima English"
  key: 2
  search-options:
    size: 3
  settings:
    highlight: matches
#    randomize-exercise-order: no
  grammar: "NovoModoPrima"
  languages:
    problem: "PrimaLat"
    solution: "PrimaEng"
  exercises:
    - problem: "vinum sapiens est"
      solution: "he is wise"
    - problem: "Augustus imperium tenet"
      solution: "the emperor holds the empire"
#    - problem: "Augustus felix est"
#      solution: "the friend is lucky"
#    - problem: "Augustus felix est"
#      solution: "the father is lucky"
#    - problem: "Augustus imperator est"
#      solution: "Augustus is a friend"
#    - problem: "Augustus amicus est"
#      solution: "Augustus is the emperor"
#    - problem: "Augustus imperator est"
#      solution: "Augustus is the father"
#    - problem: "Augustus pater est"
#      solution: "Augustus is the emperor"
#    - problem: "Caesar Augustus Galliam vincit"
#      solution: "the emperor Augustus conquers Africa"
#    - problem: "Caesar Augustus Africam vincit"
#      solution: "the emperor Augustus conquers Gaul"

- name: "Secunda"
  key: 3
  search-options:
    size: 3
  settings:
    highlight: matches
#    randomize-exercise-order: no
  grammar: "NovoModoSecunda"
  languages:
    solution: "SecundaLat"
    problem: "SecundaEng"
  exercises:
#    - solution: "feminae non manebant"
#      problem: "the Roman women stayed"
#    - solution: "libri orbi olim pulchri esse volebant"
#      problem: "the children suddenly wanted to be big"
    - solution: "iuvenis manere nolebat"
      problem: "the Roman children wanted to stay"
#    - solution: "igitur Romani gaudia Italica invitabant"
#      problem: "perhaps the Romans invited Italic joys"
    - solution: "etiam gaudium non veniebat"
      problem: "suddenly the beautiful joy comes"
- name: "Secunda English"
  key: 4
  search-options:
    size: 3
  settings:
    highlight: matches
    randomize-exercise-order: no
  grammar: "NovoModoSecunda"
  languages:
    problem: "SecundaLat"
    solution: "SecundaEng"
  exercises:
    - problem: "feminae non manebant"
      solution: "the Roman women stayed"
    - problem: "libri orbi olim pulchri esse volebant"
      solution: "the children suddenly wanted to be big"
    - problem: "iuvenis manere nolebat"
      solution: "the Roman children wanted to stay"
    - problem: "igitur Romani gaudia Italica invitabant"
      solution: "perhaps the Romans invited Italic joys"
    - problem: "etiam gaudium non veniebat"
      solution: "suddenly the beautiful joy comes"

- name: "Tertia"
  key: 5
  search-options:
    size: 5
  settings:
    highlight: matches
    randomize-exercise-order: yes
  grammar: "NovoModoTertia"
  languages:
    solution: "TertiaLat"
    problem: "TertiaEng"
  exercises:
    - solution: "Britannia est insula"
      problem: "Sweden is a peninsula"
